freecaster.tv 2011-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Extreme.com by Freecaster.tv - Where the world is watching action sports LIVE

## 1\. General Information

Zonemedia Group Limited (registered in England and Wales as Company Number 05182468), (referred to here as "we," "us" or "our") owns and operates this website (the “Site”). In order to maximise your use of the Site and for us to focus marketing initiatives and further understand how people are using the Site, we are sometimes required to collect, retain and use information about you. This Privacy Policy is designed to inform you (referred to here as "you," "your" or "yourself") about how and why we collect, manage, retain and use any information collected by us with respect to you and your use of the Site. Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy so you know what choices you have about the information we may ask you for.

We will use any personal information collected from our Site in accordance with all laws and regulations relating to the protection of personal data including the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Data Protection Act"). Further details on the Data Protection Act can be found on the Information Commissioner's website ([www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/)). Please note that the Information Commissioner’s website is not subject to our Terms of Use including this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Type of Information We Collect

(a) _Information Provided Directly by You_

When you register an account to participate in or receive a service from our Site, such as newsletters, competitions, live chats, message boards or post User Content, we ask for personal information about you. This can consist of a combination of information such as your name, e mail address, postal address, telephone or mobile number or date of birth. Different types of accounts on the Site may ask for different personal information.

By consenting to enter your details in the fields requested, you enable us to provide you with selected services. You may ‘opt in’ to receive direct emails from us and/or our selected partners. You are not required to ‘opt in’ to any services in order to register an account.

We will not disclose information provided directly by you to unrelated third parties or use the information in any other way without your prior consent.

(b) _Information on How You Use Our Site_

When you access our Site we will collect limited information about how you use the Site including details of your domain name and Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, browser version, cookie details, how long you stayed on a page, the route you took to navigate through the pages and the website that you visited prior to accessing our site. These forms of information are automatically logged by our web server and are used by us and selected partners to analyse general activity on our Site. This information is not cross-referenced with any other information which may enable you to be identified as an individual.

(c) _Cookies_

Cookies are small pieces of electronic information stored by your internet browser software on to your computer's hard drive. We access and use cookies to understand which Content, User Content, marketing and advertisements, you have seen or accessed and to help us identify unique users to our Site. We use and access cookies to enable us to provide you with personalised Content, User Content and advertising so that we can customise areas of the Site based on your previous browsing patterns. The majority of web browser software automatically accepts cookies but you can manually enable, disable or limit cookies on your computer directly. Please note that disabling cookies from your web browser may limit our ability to personalise your use of the Site.

We do not cross-reference cookies with any other information which may enable you to be identified as an individual except in circumstances where you purchase a product or service directly from us.

## 3\. Software We Use to Collect Information

Our Site uses small electronic files allowing us to count how many users have visited the Site or to access certain cookies (“web beacons”).

We use web beacons to conduct research on behalf of selected partners on their web sites and also for auditing purposes. All information recorded through a web beacon is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users to our partners. Aggregate information may include demographic, geographic and/or usage information. No personally identifiable information about you collected by a web beacon is shared with our selected partners. Where we conduct research that collects personal information we require our selected partners to disclose the presence of web beacons in their privacy policies and state what choices are available to you regarding the collection and use of this information. You may choose to opt-out of us using this information by changing your security setting on your web browser and/or operating system.

## 4\. How We Use Your Information

(a) _Managing and Optimising Our Site_

We contract with a limited amount of online partners to assist us in managing and optimising our Site. In helping us conduct market research and measure the effectiveness of our Site we use web beacons and cookies to collect information. This information helps us learn how you and other users are accessing our site, which advertising or areas of the Site are popular and how many users are responding to competitions and marketing initiatives. Although our selected online partners log the information coming from our Site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. The information provided by us to our selected online partners is anonymous. This information is not cross-referenced with any other information which may enable you to be identified as an individual by any of our selected online partners. If you would prefer not to provide us with this research and measurement information, you can "opt-out" by clicking on the following link http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

(b) _Facilitating Your Use of the Site_

We will use certain information we have collected from you or you have provided to us to help you access particular areas of the Site (Message Boards, to upload User Content etc.) and to administer contests and competitions. 

(c) _Select Marketing by Us_

In order for us to personalise your use of the Site, we may use some portions of the information we have collected from you or you have provided to us. If you choose and consent to receive email notifications from us regarding newsletters, updates, offers and rewards, we will contact you directly. Please note that we do not advocate junk mail and you may chose to stop marketing emails from us at any time by contacting us at [onlineinfo@chellozone.com](mailto:onlineinfo@chellozone.com) or you can click on the ‘unsubscribe’ link located at the bottom of the any marketing email we may send you. We will process your request as soon as possible and usually within 48 hours.

(d) _Third Party Advertising_

We may use a selected partner to manage our third party advertisements on the Site. Our partners may personalise what ads you see based on your use of this Site and other websites. This information is anonymous in that it does not include your name, street address, email address or telephone number. In order to do this, our partner may need to place a cookie on your computer. The majority of web browser software automatically accepts cookies but you can manually enable, disable or limit cookies on your computer directly. Please note that disabling cookies from your web browser may limit our ability to personalise your use of the Site.

(e) _Responding to Feedback and Requests_

If you ask us any questions or provide us with feedback, we will use your information to identify you in order for us to respond appropriately.

## 5\. Retention of Information

We will retain the information that identifies you as an individual for as long as we need to fulfil the required purpose. When you register for an account on the Site we will keep your information for as long as your account is active. If you chose to deactivate your account with us we will delete all your personal information that we possess as soon as possible. If you enter into a contest or competition we will only keep your information for the duration of that contest or competition. If you are shortlisted or win a contest or competition we will keep your information until the prizes have been delivered in full or for as long as the relevant contest or competition terms and conditions provide.

## 6\. Security

We operate a secured server on our Site and offer your information the same level of online protection as our own information. We will never ask you for account passwords in an unsolicited phone call or unsolicited email. You are responsible for keeping your password secure and you should not disclose them to anyone.

## 7 . If You Are Under 18

If you are aged 18 or under you are not permitted to register on this Site or provide us with any personal information. You are otherwise entitled to use the Site with the permission of your parent or guardian.

## 8\. Your Rights

You have the right to access your information held by us and, where necessary, to have it amended. You can also request not to receive marketing information from us. For more details, please contact: Online Department, Chellozone 105-109 Salusbury Road, London, England NW6 6RG or email [onlineinfo@chellozone.com](mailto:onlineinfo@chellozone.com)

## 9\. Chatroom, Forums, Comments and User Content

We remind you that chat rooms, forums, comments and areas of our Site that allow you to submit User Content on our Sites are for public viewing and discussion. Any personal information supplied by you in the public areas of the Site is widely accessible. We are not responsible for the information or content posted by you on the Site.

## 10\. Links to other websites

Our Sites contains links to other websites that are completely unrelated to us. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these websites nor are we responsible for the content and practices of these websites.

## 11\. Changes to our privacy statement

This Privacy Policy may change at any time, so you may wish to check it each time you visit our Site.
